soldoutaftercrisis.net 2012-09-20

# 37 Critical Items

Your privacy is critically important to us.  If you give us your name, email address, or other information, we will use it to communicate with you regarding your order status or to share other resources and offers. 

You can unsubscribe from any communications from us at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link found at the bottom of every automated email we send.

Most payments are processed through Clickbank, the world’s largest digital retailer. which uses the most advanced SSL Encrypted Security technology available so your information is always secure. See the “Security” link for more details. 

By viewing, visiting, using or interacting with this website, or any other pop-up or advertisement on this website, you are agreeing with and consent to our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change and update our Privacy Policy at any time, with or without notice. From time to time, this policy will be updated based upon new technologies, business practices, and our customers’ needs. 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or order an affiliate product from another company we are working with. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information.  You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

 To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

 To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

 To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions  
(We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes without your consent)

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.

**Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.**

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request, place an order or access your personal information. 

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Despite all of these efforts to protect your information, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk.  Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We may share or sell personally identifiable information with third parties for marketing or other purposes without your consent.

We may share information to third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at 

_[http://www.SoldOutAfterCrisis.net/terms.php](http://www.soldoutaftercrisis.net/terms.php)._

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on October 5, 2010

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information found at this link: http://www.SoldOutAfterCrisis.net/contactus.php    
3879 E. 120th Avenue  
Suite 323  
Thornton, CO 80233  
USA  
info@SoldOutAfterCrisis.net

**Privacy Policy Customer Pledge**

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the following important privacy laws and initiatives:  
Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act  
California Online Privacy Protection Act  
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act  
Privacy Alliance

Respectfully,

SoldOutAfterCrisis   
www.SoldOutAfterCrisis.net
